Dick Russell papers, Inclusive: 1924-2011, undated, Bulk: 1964-2003, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Subject Files, 1960-2011, undated; 4
  - Privacy, News Clips, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Privacy, News Clips, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Privacy, The New Yorker, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Privacy, “Privacy Journal”, 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Simpson, O.J., Case, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - TWA Flight 800, 1996-1999 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Veciana, Antonio, General, 1960-1963, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Veciana, Antonio, Alpha 66, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Veciana, Antonio, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Veciana, Antonio, Directory, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Veciana, Antonio, Interview, 1976, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Veciana, Antonio, Village Voice, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Walker, Edwin, General, 1963,1969 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Edwin, American Mercury, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Walker, Edwin, Castorr, Robert, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Walker, Edwin, Chronology, 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Walker, Edwin, Interviews, 1975-1976, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Walker, Edwin, LOOK Magazine, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Walker, Edwin, Notes, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Walker, Edwin, Weissman, Bernard, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Watergate, CIA Files, 1986-1991 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Watergate, CIA Files, 1975-1983 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Watergate, Colson, Charles, 1977-1987 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Watergate, Colson, Charles, Interview Correspondence (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Watergate, Colson, Charles, Interview Correspondence (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Watergate, Ehrilchman, John and Haldeman, Bob, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Watergate, Hughes, Howard, 1976-1979 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Watergate, Hughes, Howard, 1975-1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Watergate, Hunt, E. Howard, undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Watergate, Mexico, 1960-1976 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Watergate, Nixon Administration, undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - World History, Pre-1930s, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - World War II, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - World War II, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - World War II, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - World War II, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - World War II, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - World War II, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - World War II, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - World War II, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - World War II, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - World War II, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - World War II, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - World War II, undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Unpublished Book Projects, 1960-1998, undated; 5
  The Unpublished Book Projects series includes drafts of two unfinished book projects entitled “The Assassination Records Review Board” and “Closing In.”
  - Assassination Record Review Board, 1960-1998, undated; 1
    - General, Chapter Outline, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - General, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - General, COPA Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - General, Handwritten Notes, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - General, JFK Assassination Record Laws, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - General, JFK Resource Group Dallas, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - General, News Clippings, 1992-1994 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Article, “The Declassification of Dealey Plaza” by Charles J. Sanders & Mark S. Zaid, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Article, “The President JFK Assassination Records Collection Act of 1992” by Charles J. Sanders, Mark S. Zaid, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), H.L Hunt Papers Donation, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Advisories and Releases, 1995-1997 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Documents Disclosed Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Members and Mandate, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Public Hearing (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Public Hearing (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Russell Testimony, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - National Archives and Record Administration (NARA), Collection Lists, undated (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - National Archives and Record Administration (NARA), Correspondence, 1993,1995 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - National Archives and Record Administration (NARA), Identification Forms, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Newsletters, ARRC Quarterly, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters, PROBE vol. 2 no.4, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters, Open Secrets-Coalition on Political Assassinations (COPA) vol. 1 no.5, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Notes, Jim Nesai, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Notes, John Newman Jr., 1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Notes, Mary Ferrell, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Research, Anti-Castro Cubans, 1964-1979 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Research, Anti-Castro Cubans, 1960-1963 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Research, Anti-Castro Cubans, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Research, David Christ/Dan Caswell, 1960-1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Research, David Ferrie, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Research, House Select Committee on Assassinations, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Research, Itkin, Herbert, 1961-1970 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Research, Johnson, Priscilla, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Research, LHO, Military & Japan, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Research, Sierra Martinez, Paulino, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Research, Telephone Transcripts - LBJ, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - "Closing In", 1974-1976; 2
    - Chapter 1, Draft, The Watergate Connection, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Chapter 1, The Watergate Connection, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Chapter 1, Footnotes, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Chapter 2, Draft, The Anti-Castro Plots, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Chapter 3, Draft, The Riddle of Lee Harvey Oswald, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Chapter 6, Draft, The Prince and the Pauper, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Notes, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Pages 58-62, Draft, loose pages, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Pages 103-119, Draft, loose pages, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Research, News Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Research, Articles, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Research, CIA-Mafia- Castro and George deMohrenschildt, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 7)